What are you guys plotting?
According to Knight, you promised
to save both Lili and their mother.
But you only saved Lili...
So why is Knight fine with that?
As the first person to be taken hostage,
their mother is most likely dead already.
That's only your assumption!
Either way, that can be solved
by using the Resurrection Right.
Is that what you told Knight?!
So he thinks he'll see his mom again?
As a matter of fact, I proved to him
it was possible by killing him once.
Hang on!
How were you sure the Resurrection
Right even existed at that point?!
I wasn't, of course.
It wouldn't have mattered either way.
That's messed up!
Raion-kun.
Sudo-kun is the brains behind all this.
We'll win in the end.
It'd be wise to have faith in Sudo-kun,
if you're really as clever as you say.
Tasuketsu: Fate of the Majority
Found him! There!
Hey, Kai Kasai!
Huh? Oh... The two goofs from this morning.
You've really got some nerve!
We hired that guy you introduced us to
because he was supposed to be
some powerful Prime Right owner.
He got killed just like that
by some random bum!
Not another complaint...
I'm over here introducing people
out of my own good will,
all because you guys are so desperate
to survive the Killer Game.
My Prime Right disappeared
immediately after that guy died!
You set us up, didn't you?!
Mortgage Right
My Prime Right is the Mortgage Right.
Agreement
If someone breaks an agreement
they made with me,
Contract Breach
I gain whatever I designate as the guarantee.
Guarantee
In your case, I set up our contract
so that any injuries to the guy I introduced
would be a breach of contract.
What was your Prime Right again?
The ability to construct buildings
anywhere on land you don't own?
R-Run...
Production Attribute...
Prime Right of Superficies!
This could actually come in handy.
That was awesome, Kai!
You're the best!
Shooting Star.
Blast Raid.
Huh... I guess I was right.
The Imitation Right can recreate
attacks from games, too.
Lucky I got a hold of it.
This Prime Right was made for me.
A kid?
Hello to those of you within
a one-kilometer radius.
T-The Emperor?!
We will now begin tallying the majority.
"I own multiple Prime Rights." Yes or No?
I own multiple Prime Rights
Now... Have you figured out what's going on?
No need to be scared.
This is a negotiation.
I could use someone like you...
I'll make you my deputy officer if you can
accept the conditions I'm about to show you.
R-Really?!
Obey my every command, no matter what.
Give your life to see them through.
You can be revived
as many times as necessary.
Betray me and you'll be killed instantly.
In that case, I'll be taking
all of your Prime Rights.
I-I swear it!
Negotiation complete!
The Negotiation Right...
I was right to ask for this back.
Tasuketsu
Sis combined her Rights so I could take tally
and conduct Tasuketsu whenever
I want up to two more times.
I suppose I'll keep hunting Right owners.
Rear
For now, our team is structured
with our central members
of Gobo and Sudo in the
rear with four guards.
Middle
In the middle is Shinozaki,
who will gather information,
along with three members with enough
firepower and flexibility to move around.
Those being Ippy-hiko, Eren-chan, and Knight.
Front
And I'll be the main striker at the front
with Raion as our second brain,
and Nishime for support.
We're still heavy on defense...
It can't be helped. We gotta watch out
for both the Queen and other civilians.
A boy with eyes of the Emperor's emblem
has been spotted in eastern Adachi Ward!
Watch out!
The Emperor!
This isn't good...
Before, the Emperor could only
kill people through Tasuketsu.
Man or Woman
If he's resolved that weakness
and now works on the front line...
You are currently looking at this
screen in Tokyo Prefecture.
A question for those within the 210th floor of the Emperor's tower.
Are you part of Team Saneatsu?
The Killer Game's main objective is to
recover Rights and strengthen the Emperor.
At this rate, our chances of winning
will dwindle as time goes on.
Well this is troubling.
What now?
Even if we traced him, we can't identify their
headquarters given the Concealment Right.
Besides, the Emperor is too strong.
We have to avoid direct battle.
But idly waiting it out won't give us
any advantages in the long run...
In fact, it would end horribly.
Then our only shot is to...
Nihonyanagi, return home immediately.
I'll have someone come get you just in case.
Meet up with them on your way back.
Roger that!
Ouno, Ichinose!
You two head to the Emperor!
Hmm...
I don't see any potential prey out here...
Maybe I should head home.
You're the Emperor, aren't you?
Who are you?
Don't look at me like that...
I'm Raion Ouno. My father was
Hyogo Ouno, an auditor for the Camp.
The Camp?!
Gotcha!
I don't know what you're talking about.
Come on, don't play dumb.
I'm talking about the facility
the Emperor was born in.
The giant circular facility built 100 meters
underground at the border of Tokyo and Chiba.
They abducted people and
experimented on them
to facilitate the obtainment of the Rights.
How did you find me here?
You held a tally just a second ago.
It was a close call. Had the scope
been a bit larger, I'd be a goner.
I figured seeing you was some kind of fate.
You see, I wanted to apologize...
Apologize?
For the inhumane treatment you suffered
at the hands of people
at the Camp, of course.
This kid's got some balls...
I didn't expect him to start
bluffing to his face.
This is the Emperor we're dealing with!
That apology might be odd coming
from another victim, but...
It was my own family's doing, after all.
What?
I was almost another one
of their guinea pigs.
But I was saved thanks to
a dispute among the higher ups.
I can't imagine a normal citizen
approaching the Emperor by choice.
He's either actually from the Camp,
or he could be working with
that group who killed me.
Maybe I should mention some information
that only core members knew.
There are 666 Rights total! How's that?
No way!
This guy has classified
information on the Camp!
He must really be a son
of the Camp's auditor.
Who knows if he's trustworthy,
but he's definitely legit.
Looks like it actually worked.
Didn't take much.
If you find any solace in others
who suffered the same fate as you,
I'm gonna exploit that.
Fine... I'll trust you
if you agree to negotiate.
The Negotiation Right...
I figured that'd be your next play.
Only if the conditions are up to me.
What?
Promise that you won't do anything
to put me in harm's way from now on.
That's pretty demanding.
In return, I'll join your side.
I won't lie.
And I'll promise never to betray you.
Fine, negotiation complete!
What a dope... I never said anything
about negotiating with you, Emperor.
Maybe you should pay attention
to where people are pointing
before finalizing your negotiations.
Now, the Emperor can't hurt me
in return for my loyalty... to Ryuta!
People can lie with more
than just words, you know.
Total immunity from
the Emperor's attacks at no risk...
Thanks, chump!
Tasuketsu: Fate of the Majority
Now. What to do next...
I've actually infiltrated
the current Emperor's team.
Really?!
That's good to hear!
How much information
have you gathered so far?
Nothing major, just the basics.
It's a mix of newbies and veterans.
But the core veterans are withholding any
information unrelated to the tasks at hand.
That makes sense.
I'm confident I could kill them off
now if I wanted to, but...
They got me once before
because I let my guard down.
Here's what we'll do!
You come back to headquarters with me.
There, you can tell us about
the fake Emperor and their team.
Afterwards, you go back to their headquarters
and continue infiltrating them.
So I'll be your spy...
Okay, you better protect me then.
You're the only one I trust right now.
You too, huh?
I can't say I fully trust
the Queen's servants, either.
Aren't you on their team, though?
I've always worked alone.
My servant puppets were destroyed,
so the only ones I trust now are the Queen
and the civilian I picked up a second ago.
Gotcha. Then, do you mind
if I come back again later?
Why's that?
We have curfews every time we go out.
They may get suspicious
if I don't get back soon.
I see.
Then come back here again later.
I'll come get you.
Okay.
I'll be here around 23:30. Does that work?
No problem.
I'll tell the Queen our plans.
Hey. Glad you kept up with me.
It's not as easy without a plan in place.
The subway?
Yeah, it's not like the trains are running.
Let's walk the tracks back home just in case.
But man, that was some work
you did back there!
The Emperor won't be able
to attack you at all now,
and you've been invited into enemy
quarters with his full support.
Doesn't change the fact that it's scary.
I bet we're really close to winning now.
I hope so, but...
Who knows how the Queen will respond.
Jeez, your Fusion Right sure is useful.
Isn't it?
Hey, Ryuta...
I know, we're on the same page.
He's the one who pushed humanity
to the brink of extinction.
And the one who killed Sane and Saaya.
Yeah...
He's the one who killed Kazuki, too.
Don't be reckless, no matter what.
Yeah, don't worry.
I'll keep my feelings hidden.
I'll go in unarmed, without
any receivers or anything.
Beyond that, let's just hope
the Emperor protects me.
Why are you going at 23:30?
I'll keep the Emperor busy to prevent
Tasuketsu from happening at 23:55.
Makes sense!
Good thinking!
Shouldn't we have someone follow him?
That's too dangerous.
I'll watch over him
with my Visualization Right.
As long as I'm alive, I promise
to be back tomorrow before noon,
so wait for me through the morning.
Obviously, you'll know
my fate if I'm not back.
But If I were to come back after noon...
Don't hold your breath. Assume
it's someone else and kill them.
I admire your conviction.
We're counting on you, Raion-kun.
Like you told me before,
to maintain the upper hand,
we'll have to bluff a little.
Like I thought. We're transporting
with the Exchange Right.
I'm glad we didn't have anyone follow us.
All right. Let's do this.
Shinozaki here.
Confirming transportation
with the Exchange Right.
My Presentation Right went dark, too.
They must have entered the concealed area.
You got this, Raion.
So she's... Queen Kisaragi.
That's Kou Kirishima and...
Seraphiel.
You must be Raion Ouno.
That's right.
Like I told you this afternoon,
we've already established his loyalty
with my Negotiation Right.
There's nothing to worry about, Sis.
Huh? Sis?!
Did I forget to tell you?
Don't tell anyone.
Y-Yeah, sure...
That makes the Emperor
another cousin of Yagihashi's.
What the hell's going on with that family?
I see.
So you're the one who
challenged me to a bargain.
I didn't think you were
on the Emperor's side, so...
You know Tojuro Yagihashi, then?
Yeah... But he's been a hard guy to read.
So we've got the Fusion Right,
Rejection Right, Materialization Right,
Response Right, Suspension Right,
and the Presentation Right.
Man, Raion. They only
told you about six Rights?
Sorry, I'll try to get as many as I can.
I'm counting on you.
Where's the bathroom?
Outside and in the building to your right.
Okay, thanks.
All right, now what?
I don't have much time.
I gotta get to the point.
Who do we have here?!
Hey there!
No worries, it's just space division.
Division... The Division Right!
This guy must be Ren Iruga!
Judging from your reaction...
You must be Raion-kun.
Wait! How do you know who I—
I have a bit of a connection
with the President.
With Yagihashi?!
Pres predicted you'd eventually
come here a long, long time ago.
He seems to trust your lying quite a bit.
Then...
Yagihashi actually depends on my lies?
What he said were actually instructions
knowing I could win over the Emperor?
Yagihashi... Iruga... And given those
instructions, Sudo must be involved, too.
What a brutal trio... Jeez.
Come with me.
Iruga, you're here.
Ebina! And Hirayama?!
I've heard the gist
about you guys from Knight.
I don't have much time, so let's be quick.
Right. We want you guys to take down
the Emperor and Seraphiel.
Are we gonna split up and fight?
Lady Kisaragi and Kou are usually together.
Besides, you guys are more
familiar with the Emperor,
and we're more familiar
with Lady Kisaragi.
What about the other guys?
I hate to say it,
but our hands are too full.
We have to ask your side
to take care of the others.
We'll have a backup plan, just in case.
Once we've gathered enough information,
we'll plan for Hikari's escape.
No matter what, we'll make sure
that information gets to you guys.
That's enough for the time being.
Knight better be safe over there.
Don't worry about him.
He's running around our
headquarters safe and sound.
Hey, Raion! You still in there?!
Damn it! It's the Emperor!
Now, now, no need to panic.
We're in a whole other space.
I'll let you out on your own, Raion-kun.
Oh, there you are. What are you doing?
U-Um, I couldn't find the bathroom
so I went outside. My bad...
You're not as sharp as I thought, Raion!
Shouldn't you get back pretty soon?
I'll take you back.
It'll be a quick jump
with Meguru's Prime Right.
The innocent way he laughed just now...
You know, that power really comes in handy.
The reason he's friendly towards me isn't
just because he used the Negotiation Right.
Besides, who doesn't dream
about teleporting?
It's like, we can do anything you see
in manga and games with Prime Rights.
He thinks of me as a friend
around the same age as him.
Kinda like I did with Tasuketsu.
They said he suffered all alone all that time.
Oh yeah, I have another Right
called the Imitation Right.
Does this mean he's sincerely
happy to have me here?
It's awesome, I can even recreate
attacks from games and stuff.
Damn it... Why?
I'll show you next time.
The Emperor killed Kazuki...
And billions of other people...
So then why...
Why does my heart sting like this?
Confirming return.
Welcome back, for real!
Glad to see you're safe.
Where are the others?
Should I share my report tomorrow?
No, let's go over the main points now.
The infiltration was successful.
I met the Queen and them, too.
Along with a few others, but...
Any details you can share with us?
Internal information or anything.
Yeah... To start, there was
another head to count.
His name was Kai Kasai.
He's a new officer to the Emperor.
He has the ability to steal others' Rights
if they break agreements with him.
It's called the Mortgage Right.
Sounds pretty powerful.
Mm-yup...
I met with Hirayama and Hikari, too.
Knight's story was true.
Hirayama's side will take down
the Queen and Kou.
He wants us to deal with
the Emperor and Seraphiel.
Hmm... I see.
That's not going to be easy.
Which reminds me, Yagihashi.
You know the Emperor's real name, don't you?
It'd be misleading to say
I "know" him, but...
By that, I'm guessing it's Haruto-kun?
How does the President know the Emperor?
The Emperor Haruto Yanagi is
the Queen Maria Kisaragi's little brother.
Which means he's Yagihashi's cousin!
The Queen and Emperor are siblings?!
And they're both cousins of Pres?!
I wasn't aware of that fact,
but it sounds like it.
But more importantly, who was closer
to the Queen, Kou or Seraphiel?
Did he say "more importantly"?
Kou was.
That's why Hirayama decided to take the two
of them and asked us to deal with Seraphiel.
I see. I understand very well.
Raion-kun, your efforts
surpassed my expectations.
He sure looks satisfied.
So he used me to sniff out
information he was looking for.
This connects...
Innocence
every piece of the puzzle.